Downloaded @ subs4free.club
Subtitles by explosiveskull
@ subs4free.info
There are
moments in our lives...
that seem to define us.
Moments we keep going back to.
My life before him was
so simple and decided.
And now, after him,
there's just...
after.
Tessa!
Okay, what are we forgetting?
- Hairdryer.
- Nope.
Flashlight.
Mom, it's college, it's
not a survival course.
Towels. Battery charger.
Phone charger.
I can always drive
anything up, if you forget it.
Okay, we should get going.
We have a long drive ahead.
Let's do a last
minute room check.
- Oh, wait, Mom...
- Thank you.
- We're on the right floor.
- B-22...
B-22...
Um...
B-22.
22... there it is.
Hi.
Hi. Um...
Steph?
In the flesh.
I'm Tessa.
It's my new roomie.
This is Tristan.
Hey.
- Hi. I'm Tessa.
Come in, we're not gonna bite.
Oh, sorry.
Uh, so this is my mom
and this is Noah.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Full disclosure.
I was pretty bummed to be
paired with a freshman.
Then I thought,
hello, bright side...
I'm going to be
your spirit guide.
We can get you into all the
best places even without a fake.
No problem.
Mom?
I like your sweater.
Thanks, I got it from the Gap.
Cute.
We're going straight down to
the housing office right now...
and requesting a room change.
Wait, what are you
talking about?
That room reeked of weed,
and you will not...
Can you please not make a scene?
I'm not, we have worked
too hard for this...
Okay, okay...
and I don't want you to be
distracted by anyone.
Mom, this is me
that we're talking about.
Can you please just trust me?
It'll be fine, I promise...
promise.
House is gonna be
so empty without you.
I know. I'll miss you.
Oh, god, I am so proud of you.
Thanks, Mom.
Okay. I love you, my baby.
I'm going. See you later.
Bye.
I got it.
This is the part
I've been dreading.
Me, too.
Oh, I was actually talking about
the ride home with your mom.
Okay.
How much did I
freak your mom out?
Um...
She thinks I'm going
to be a bad influence?
She's just very protective.
It's always only
been the two of us.
No, no, thanks.
See? Seems like she
has nothing to worry about.
Your brother's cute.
Oh, you mean Noah, no,
he's my boyfriend.
Shit, sorry.
No, it's okay. He's a
senior in high school.
It's Tristan.
I was supposed to meet her.
What's with all the old books?
Who brings books to college?
Me, I guess.
The bookish vibe, I like that.
Alright, I'm out.
Okay, bye.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Econ 101?
Yeah.
It's locked, yeah,
I already tried it.
Right.
Couple of early birds, huh?
Have fun in there.
- Sorry, after you.
- Oh, after you.
- No, no, honestly, I insist.
- No, I insist.
- No, honestly...
- My mother raised me to...
Okay.
Are you a first year, too?
Yeah. Are you an Econ major?
That's the plan, you?
I'm an English major.
I'm Landon, by the way.
Tessa, hi.
Hi, nice to meet you.
Good morning,
I'm Professor Alexander...
and welcome to Econ 101.
This might be the most important
class you take here...
so I expect everyone here
to closely pay attention...
and benefit from the 25-year
career I had on Wall Street.
Now let's get started.
Uh, excuse me.
Uh, I think that you're
in the wrong room.
I'm in the right room.
How did you even get in here?
Okay. Can you please go out into
the hall, so I can get dressed?
Don't flatter yourself,
I'm not looking.
You took your time.
There they are. Hey, Tessa.
Hi, uh, can you please ask your
boyfriend to leave...
so I can get dressed?
Uh, not my boyfriend.
What did you say to her?
Nothing. I've been
minding my own business.
Okay, well, whoever he is.
You're going out
with us tonight.
Yeah, I don't know.
I'm trying to picture
this one at a party.
Just not seeing it.
You're not going to stay
in here forever, right?
Nope.
The Great Gatsby...
it's a good book.
Hate to spoil it...
but it was all a dream.
Actually...
it was all a lie.
What's he looking at?
Hello, can I get a
Cappuccino with almond milk...
add cinnamon on
top? Sure thing.
I'll have a regular
black coffee, please.
And for you?
Can I have
an Americano, please?
No problem.
Thanks.
Ooh, such a player.
- Now pick it up.
- Thank you.
You're picking us
up, right, Zed?
When am I
picking you guys up?
I don't know, 8:00?
Guess what?
Ssh!
We're gonna go to
a party tonight.
I don't know.
You're going, don't
you want to have fun?
Ssh!
You, ssh!
Yeah, of course, I do.
Then grab your shit...
Yes, okay... okay.
Let's get ready to party.
What do you think? What?
It's... it's pretty.
Maybe it's just a
little too formal.
You said be myself.
You know what, I
love it. I love it.
Oh, isn't it crazy?
- Hey!
- Hey. What's up?
Chug, chug, chug, chug!
Ooh, chug, chug, chug.
There's my baby.
Wow, wow.
Hey, what's up?
- Hi, Tessa.
- Hi.
I need things to be
way less in focus.
Do that again, do that again.
Do it again? I'm
dying over here.
Do it! I want to get
it on the camera.
Sick, bro.
Hey, guys, this is my
new roommate, Tessa.
This is everybody.
Nice to meet you, my name's Zed.
You've met
Hardin, and that's Molly.
Hey.
You want to sit down?
Cute dress.
Oh, yeah, and that's
Jace... the Townie.
What's up?
What's your major, Tessa?
Um, I'm thinking business
or maybe economics.
Very cool.
You want a drink?
I don't really drink.
Come on, we're all
drinking, have a drink.
She doesn't drink?
Just a shot.
Do it, come on.
- Just a small one.
Oh, my god, Steph, where'd
you find this girl?
No one's talking to you.
Oh... yes!
Cheers to that.
You okay?
Ooh, babe.
Aw, poor baby.
You're so pretty.
Okay, so, um, guys...
truth or dare?
What?
Truth or dare?
- No, no!
- Come on.
Isn't this a kid's game?
Not the way we play.
Hey, Tessa, truth or dare?
Truth.
Craziest place you've had sex.
Um, pass.
Why, it's an easy one.
Wait... are you a virgin?
- I'll do dare.
- Dare, hm.
I dare you to make
out with Hardin.
She won't do it.
This never ends well.
Do you want to do this?
You having fun, Molly?
I'm done playing this game.
Oooh,
sucks to suck.
I like this girl.
Hardin Scott got
his first rejection.
Denied, bro.
Hey.
Hey, I
thought we were gonna Facetime?
Yeah, sorry.
Where are you right
now? It's really loud.
Um, I'm with Steph,
and her friends...
but they're all just
like... I don't know.
So, you're at a party?
Have you been drinking?
I just had one drink.
Okay, so you go to college...
and now you drink, that's...
that's really great, Tessa.
Noah, can you not be so like...
So like what? I'm not the one
who's out partying right now.
Just forget it.
- Tessa, I want...
My bad.
- What are you doing?
- Hm?
Nothing.
Are you looking for something?
Are you drunk?
I don't drink...
just like you don't.
"He's more myself than I am.
Whatever our souls are made of.
"His and mine are the same."
It's Bronte, Teresa?
I know it's Bronte...
and my name is Tessa.
What were you doing
in my room, Tessa?
Your room?
Yes.
Are we still playing?
'Cause I think
you owe me a dare.
Wait, I can't.
I need to go.
Don't
doubt me, I got this...
look, look, here we go, ready?
Oh! Nice
shot, all right.
Hi.
Hey, I'm glad I'm not the
only freshman in this class.
Yeah, I'm psyched
I got in. Yeah.
All right, folks,
let's get started...
Jane Austen's masterpiece.
Who in here has already
read Pride and Prejudice?
And what did you think
of it on the first read?
Let's hear from our
newcomer, Mr. Scott.
Pride and Prejudice... Elizabeth
Bennett needs to chill.
She gave Darcy a way worse
time than he deserved.
Are you saying that Darcy was
not in love with Elizabeth?
Love is just a transaction...
we're all hardwired to desire.
We present the correct set of
desirable traits and boom...
we can turn it on and
we can turn it off.
Yes. Ms. Young? Tessa?
I think that it was the most
revolutionary feminist novel...
that I've ever read, that a
woman of that era would have...
the strength to reject Darcy
when he treated her poorly.
That's a load.
It was Darcy's very attitude
that attracted Elizabeth to him.
Darcy's attitude was
rude and mocking.
I think that he was lucky
to be with a woman...
with as much integrity
as Elizabeth.
The only reason he even
asked her to marry him...
was 'cause she wouldn't
stop throwing herself...
Throwing herself at him?
He was pursuing her.
She's clearly not
satisfied with her life...
and is looking for excitement
wherever she can get it.
Well, I think that it's
obviously all in his head...
that she had any
feelings for him at all.
Well, there you have it.
That's the power of a good book.
That was exciting.
No, it was annoying.
I enjoyed it.
Look, whatever you're
thinking, don't.
Nothing happened between us.
Okay? I have a boyfriend.
Us... I thought we were talking
about Pride and Prejudice.
Hey, do you want to
go get some coffee?
How can someone be so arrogant?
"Elizabeth Bennett
needs to chill."
Like who even...
who even says that?
That's just Hardin
being Hardin.
You know him?
Yeah, we're, uh, we're
practically related.
My mom is dating
Chancellor Scott.
Chancellor Scott
is Hardin's dad...
and Hardin and I, we tolerate
each other, but barely.
His father's the chancellor?
Yeah.
Listen, Tessa, he's just
trying to get a reaction.
Well, he's not gonna
get one from me.
Hm...
Agh!
It actually does hurt.
You should get one.
My mom would literally kill me.
You need to get this.
I bet you'd love that one.
Yeah, dice...
I feel like my mom has
everything planned out for me.
Like, I think she's been
planning my wedding
to Noah since we were five.
Wait, is Noah the only dude
you've ever gone out with?
That's sad.
Ooh, ow!
Watch it.
Yeah, you guys really
aren't selling me on this.
Ssh! You
look so good tonight.
Shh!
Can I get a
small coffee, please?
Here you go.
Yeah, thanks.
- Hi.
I can't stay away from you.
What?
Well, we're gonna
see each other.
I'm friends with Steph
and you're roommates.
Tessa, let's just start over,
just reset and we can be...
What... friends?
Why not?
I want to show you something.
So show me then.
It's a... it's a place.
I think that it's better
if we keep our distance.
I'll see you around.
It's down this way. Come on.
Welcome to my favorite place.
It's beautiful.
- How about a swim?
- Hm?
What are... what are you doing?
I'm going swimming.
Hardin...
Hardin.
Come in.
You can wear my t-shirt.
It feels amazing.
A little privacy, please?
Okay.
What?
I like it better on you.
Can I ask you something?
Do I even have a choice?
Who do you love the
most in the world?
Easy... myself.
Of course, you do.
What's your boyfriend's name?
It's Noah.
Noah... does he go here?
He's in high school.
High school?
And what does a high school
kid do to deserve you?
He is nice to me.
Nice?
Isn't that just another
word for boring?
Not always.
Can I show you something?
Hold your breath.
Silence... it's peaceful.
You think that's weird?
No... not at all.
I thought that you just
wanted to be friends.
I don't think we can
ever be just friends.
Have you never been
touched before?
Why'd you stop?
We've got time.
So, why do you
call them "chips"?
Why do you call them "fries"?
Because they're fried.
They're not French.
You've got plenty there.
Hey, uh, I ordered
mine without ketchup.
Oh, right, I'll be right back.
Thank you.
No ketchup?
That's very un-American.
I'm full of surprises.
So... what's your story then?
My story?
Yeah. Like, your family?
How you ended up here?
Pass.
I just don't think asking a
bunch of arbitrary questions...
about someone's past is really
gonna tell you who they are.
I can find out who you
are by sitting here...
and spending time with you.
What?
What are you doing?
I'm just waiting for you to
reveal your true self to me...
by just sitting here and
spending time with you.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Okay, fair enough...
one question.
Why do you have all
those romance novels...
if you don't believe in love?
Who says I don't
believe in love?
You did, in Soto's class.
True.
Maybe don't believe
everything I say then.
Oh, hey, guys.
Hey, Tessa.
Guys, let's just hang
out for a minute.
So... what have
you two been up to?
- We were just...
- We're just getting some food.
Oh, how's the boyfriend, Tess?
We're leaving.
Perfect. I need a ride.
It's not a good time, you
can ask Zed for a ride.
Dude, we literally
just got here.
Excuse me.
You're excused.
All right... Tessa?
Really?
Yes, I won't be long.
I'll be at the bar.
See you around.
What's up, bro?
So, fill us in.
- What was that?
- What was what?
Were you like embarrassed
that they saw us together?
No.
You know, I'm going to tell
Noah about us, I just...
Us? What do you mean "us"?
If you want to dump Mr. High
School, then go ahead...
but don't do it on my account.
What?
Look, it was fun,
but I don't date.
Are you actually kidding me?
You're here.
What are you dreaming about?
Surprise!
What... what are you...
what are you doing here?
How are you?
Thank you.
Are you okay?
Yeah. No, yeah, yeah, of course.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Yeah.
So, what are we gonna do?
Hey,
there's Tessa.
What's
up, Tessa?
Hey.
Hi.
We met at the dorm.
- So, he does exist.
- Nice to meet you.
What's up, man, it's
Zed, how's it going?
Good, how are you doing?
Cool, campfire.
Tessa.
Thanks.
Cops will probably
be here soon, so...
Oh, should we get out of here?
Hey, Tessa, didn't
expect to see you here.
So, how about we play a
game of Suck and Blow?
Suck and Blow, I'm down.
Okay, I got it.
- Yes!
- Aww.
Guess you know what that
means. Oh, no, no, I'm...
Whoa, dude, dude, dude...
Leave it, Jace.
Don't go there, all right?
Chill out, man,
it's just a game, man.
- Hey, man, she doesn't have...
- Leave it, Jace.
Relax, dude. Hey, relax.
Whoa! Hey!
Hey, hey, hey, get off!
You're
gonna regret this.
Dude, you're freaking!
What are you doing, man?
- Hardin?
And the referee
gives a yellow card!
This crowd is not happy at all.
Hey, thanks for coming.
What happened?
Uh, well, it started
about his father
and then your name
sort of came up.
He won't talk to me
so I figured maybe
he would talk to you.
Where is he?
What are you doing here?
I was worried about you.
Shouldn't you be
with your perfect
little boyfriend, Teresa?
Don't bring Noah into this.
I thought you didn't drink.
I don't.
I didn't what does it matter?
You made a real mess in there.
I was celebrating.
Didn't you hear?
Dear old Dad is getting married.
You should see the dump my poor
mom lives in back in London.
Don't you feel like
you've had enough?
Don't, I can get it.
Ow, damn it.
Come with me.
I'm sorry for how I treated you.
Um, if... if you don't date,
if that's how you feel...
I don't think that is
how I feel anymore.
I'm a mess.
I think that we're both a mess.
You don't ever have to
cover up, not for me.
Hey. You okay?
Yeah.
Where were you, I texted
you, you didn't answer me.
Um, I'm sorry. My
phone died, I'm sorry.
Where were you?
A friend needed my help.
But... in the middle
of the night?
Noah, I can explain, can we...
Please, can we just...
can we just go inside and talk?
I don't...
No...
I don't believe this.
No, Noah...
Noah, wait.
Noah, I'm...
I'm confused.
I wanted to talk to you
about it for a while.
I am so, so sorry.
Noah...
Tessa...
Go home, Hardin.
Noah and I just broke up.
I feel like I just
lost my best friend.
Come over here.
I didn't expect to see you.
When my dad left, I was 10.
He left us with nothing.
And my mom, she just
sort of fell apart.
I had to take
care of her alone
but Noah was there
for me, you know?
I hate myself for
what I did to him.
Tessa, it's not your fault.
Yeah, it is.
Noah's my best friend.
But you...
You're so much more.
Library is closing.
Library is
getting ready to close.
Library is closing!
- Follow me.
- Hm?
- Come on.
- What are...
Down here.
Ssh.
"You could draw me to fire.
You could draw me to water.
"You could draw
me to the gallows.
"You could draw me to any death.
"You could draw me to
anything I've most avoided.
"This and the confusion
of my thoughts.
"So that time fit for
nothing is what I mean
"by your being the ruin of me."
Why'd you stop?
We should go.
Hey! What are you
doing here? Stop!
Perhaps the most
mesmerizing of all things
is the binary star couple.
Two stars find their way
across vast stretches of space
and time to find
another wandering body
and become attached for
eternity in each others' orbit.
Each star pushing the other
to explode in supernova...
becoming either the
nucleus of planetary nebula
or just as often,
resulting in a death spiral.
What are you doing,
Tessa? Learning about the stars?
The stars assist
in each others' system.
Do you have any idea
how beautiful you are right now?
What are you always
writing in there?
None of your business.
- Show me.
- No.
- Come on!
- No chance!
I just want to see what's...
Tessa, hun?
I've called all the... Tessa?
Mom? What are you doing here?
What the hell is going on?
Nothing.
Who's he? Is he the
guy Noah told me about?
So this is how you spend your
time instead of going to class?
No!
- I think I should go.
You think?
Can we talk about this
outside please? Please!
You, go! Come with me.
You have got to be kidding me.
I knew as soon as I
saw that roommate
that something like
this would happen.
Are you serious right now?
And after all this work
and you are gonna throw
it away for some boy!
What are you talking
about? I'm not.
You're going to break
up with this boy
and you are going to
focus on your schoolwork.
Do you even know what it
has been like trying to be
perfect for you,
having you mold my life
into the way that
you wanted it to be?
I did it for your own good.
I am so, so sorry, Mom, that
your life didn't work out
the way that you wanted
it to, I really am
but this is my life and
you have to let me live it.
Is that really what you want?
Yes.
If I leave now, you're cut off.
He's gonna break your heart.
She's cutting
you off because of Hardin.
I'm just a little
worried, is all?
Why?
Hardin is...
Hardin is complicated.
Yeah, I know, but he's
different around me.
Just be careful.
You okay?
Yeah. Where have you been?
Jump in and I'll show you.
- You ready?
- Yes!
- Are you sure?
Who's place is this?
A friend of my
father's, a professor.
Where are they?
She's in Italy. Oh yeah, I'm
meant to be watering the plants.
Ooh, she paints.
It's really nice.
Imagine if it were our place.
Sure.
It can be.
What, you mean,
like live together?
When you told me your mom
was going to cut you off
I had to do something.
We can stay here for
the rest of the year
just you and me.
You did this for me?
- Here.
- Mm-hm.
You're gonna bring out
the best of our loves.
Mm-hm.
Whoa!
Look at that one.
It looks a bit like you.
This is crazy.
I still can't believe it.
Hm? Believe what?
That you're mine.
Not this again.
I don't deserve you.
Nothing could ever change the
way that I feel about you.
- I can not believe you've
talked me into this.
- It's a wedding reception,
it's not a jail sentence.
Hey!
- Hey, you guys made it.
- Yeah.
- You look beautiful, Tessa.
- Oh, thank you.
Hey, you clean up well, man.
This is so fancy.
Yeah, it's beautiful.
So we're brothers.
Yeah.
You must be really happy
for your mom and Ken.
Yeah, yeah, I am.
I'll see you two in there.
This looks so good.
Look who's here.
It's good to see you.
You, too.
And you must be...
- Tessa.
Tessa.
Tessa, I'm Karen.
- Hi.
- I'm Landon's mom.
- It's so nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
It means a lot to me
that you could be here.
Congratulations.
Thanks for coming.
I'm happy you decided
to join us, son.
Landon tells us you're in
Professor Soto's seminar.
Yeah.
So, you're an English major?
Um, I would love to, but I think
if I want to be employed
maybe business or econ.
If you're interested in the
business side of literature
my friend owns a
publishing company.
You mean Vance?
- Yes.
Well, I can call Vance for her.
Of course, I'm sure he'd
be happy to hear from you.
Ken, Dana's arrived.
I think we should go say hi.
Enjoy.
- Nice meeting you.
- Yeah, you too.
Let's just have fun.
I can't.
Why not?
You made me promise to
be on my best behavior.
Thank you all for coming.
Tonight we celebrate
great, good fortune
and her name is Karen.
The love of my life and...
and frankly she saved my life.
I'm suddenly blessed by a
new bride, a new life and
not one, but two
brilliant sons...
Hardin and Landon.
I remember an earlier time
when my greatest pleasure
was to listen to Hardin,
who loved to recite passages
from novels, all by memory
and he would perform
them, leaving me with tears...
He's not the man I grew up with.
- or laughter.
My father was a drunk
and nothing more.
At least he's trying
which is more than
my father ever did.
People change.
Clearly, but that still
doesn't change what happened.
What happened?
One night, when I was eight
my dad was at the pub,
drunk as usual.
He messed with the wrong guys.
They came to our
house for payback.
He wasn't there.
They found my mom instead.
I tried...
I tried to fight them
off, but I couldn't.
Thank you, my friends, my
family and university faculty.
And that's my dad, the
beloved Chancellor Scott.
Let's have fun!
I don't suppose you recall
any of those passages.
Not the way you remember it.
I would love to have a dance
with your brilliant son.
I want you now.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Do you want me to stop?
No, just go slow.
- Car.
- It was "cat".
Do another one.
Uh-that one is...
- I have no idea!
- I'm really good at this, yeah.
Okay, just do one more,
I promise, I'll get it.
Um...
Hm I don't know, what was it?
Can always stay up
late and work on that.
- I'll just see you.
- I'll text you.
Hey.
How's it going? I haven't seen
you since like the bonfire.
Yeah, I've been busy, I guess.
How's it going with you
and your boyfriend?
Uh, we're not together anymore.
Ouch. Bye-bye, high school.
Yeah, it was pretty painful.
Yeah, I can tell you
moved on pretty quickly.
How's Hardin?
What do you mean?
He told me you guys
have been hanging out.
Yeah, we have.
Cool.
Really?
Yeah, I mean Hardin
does what Hardin does.
What's wrong?
What's all this about?
What didn't you tell me?
Nothing. I don't know
what she's talking about.
You don't know what
she's talking about?
- I mean, I don't know.
- What didn't you tell me?
Nothing.
I need to go.
What, now? Hardin, answer me!
Where are you going?
- Out.
- What's going on?
Do you trust me?
Of course, I do, I just...
Then what's the problem?
What are you doing
in Hardin's car?
What, I can't borrow his car?
Jace, just tell me where he is!
Maybe he's at Blind Bob's.
Oh, my gosh, hey.
What's the matter?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
You want some fries,
are you hungry?
I haven't seen
you since you moved out.
Um, I've been living
with Hardin off-campus.
Wait, you two are
living together?
Yeah.
Wow, Tessa, I didn't know
you two were that serious.
Yeah, we are.
How long has
this been going on for?
Look who I found.
Oh, hey, Jace, hi, Hardin.
- What's up? What's up, Tessa?
- You are very talented.
I got you.
Tessa?
Hi, Hardin.
Tessa was just
telling us the latest.
Tessa's been filling us
in on all the details.
Moving in together?
And you guys are so adorable.
Is there anything you
want to tell Tessa?
Yeah, like what's been going
on between you and her?
Nothing's going on
with me and her.
Well, I don't believe you.
What have you said?!
- Tessa, I swear...
- I saw the texts that she sent.
What te... they
didn't mean anything.
I didn't even reply to
them, they meant nothing.
- You're kidding me.
- Tessa, nothing's going on.
Don't you think this thing
has gone a little too far?
What thing, Hardin?
Something's going on, but
it's not what you think.
Molly, shut up.
Tessa, let's get out of
here and I'll explain.
I'll explain
everything, I promise.
Remember truth or dare?
What?
Molly, don't.
Molly!
I'm done playing this game.
- Oh!
- I like this girl.
Looks like Hardin Scott
just got his first rejection.
You don't think I
can make it happen?
Make what
happen, Hardin?
Here's a dare: make her
fall in love with me
and then, I'll just...
turn it off.
It was all a game.
Tessa, Tessa...
Tessa, please you
have to believe me.
Tessa, that was
before everything,
before I got to know you.
Is that true?
And all of you knew?
Tessa.
Tessa, wait. Tessa!
So, what exactly did
you tell them, then?
Nothing.
None of it was real.
I actually thought...
I thought that...
You're just a liar.
That was all before...
Before what?
Before...
You snapped your fingers
and you turned it off.
You said nothing could change
the way you felt about me.
Then, I guess we're both liars.
Hi, Mom.
What happened?
I don't really want
to talk about it.
I just... I came here
to say that I'm sorry.
I'm... I'm sorry, too.
I love you.
So how come you're back?
I just needed to come home.
I'm so sorry, Noah.
I never meant to hurt you.
Yeah, I know.
I guess I just never
saw any of this coming.
Yeah, but that's
like the point, right?
We like... we change and
we discover who we are.
I think that's okay.
Yeah?
Yeah.
On a parting note,
I was deeply impressed by all
of your papers attacking our
themes for this semester.
Congratulations on
all of your good work.
Miss Young?
This is what Hardin turned in.
I think it was actually written
more for you than it was for me.
Thank you.
What is that?
Oh, a secret spot, and
a good place to think.
I've read
hundreds of novels in my life.
Most of them claiming that love
was the center of the universe.
That it could heal any
damage inside of us.
That it was what
we need to survive.
From Darcy to Heathcliff,
I thought they were fools.
That love was
something fictional
only found in worn
pages of a book.
But that has all changed since
I met my Elizabeth Bennet.
I never thought I would
find myself completely
and utterly consumed
by another until her.
She took my hand and led
me out of the darkness
and showed me that whatever
our souls are made of
hers and mine are the same.
I'm sorry. Please forgive me.
You once asked who I
loved most in this world.
It's you.
Subtitles by explosiveskull
@ subs4free.info